PRIVACY POLICY
==============

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) will explain how we process and collect your (“user”, “you” or “your”) data when you install and use our Becovi browser extension and any other feature or service that we Becovi offer or provide you with therein (collectively “Extension”), as well as how such data may be used or shared with others, how we safeguard it and you may exercise your rights related to your Personal Data (as such term is defined below), among others, according to the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) and the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) where applicable.

In the event you are a California resident and the CCPA apply to you – please review our [CCPA Privacy Notice](https://www.becovi.com/ccpa_privacy_notice.php)

This Policy is an integral part of the Extension’s [Terms and Conditions](https://www.becovi.com/terms.php) (“Terms”). Unless otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms used herein but not defined herein shall have the meaning ascribed to them in the Terms. YOUR PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO US AND WE THEREFORE ENCOURAGE YOU TO READ THIS POLICY THOROUGHLY BEFORE YOU INSTALL OR USE OUR EXTENSION.

We reserve the right to periodically amend or revise the Policy. The revised terms will be effective immediately upon the display of the revised Policy. The last revision date will be reflected in the “Last Modified” heading. In the event of amendments that will majorly change our privacy practices, we will make a reasonable effort to provide an applicable notification of such amendment. We recommend you review this Policy periodically to check for any such amendment.

The use of information received from Google API will adhere the Chrome Web Store User Data Policy including the Limited Use requirements.

The following are the ways in which we collect your data and why we process your data:
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

We may collect certain types of data from you when you download or use the Extension that may be considered to be one of the following: (i) Information that identifies a person or can with a reasonable amount of effort identify a person (“**Personal Data**”); (ii) information that is collected and processed by us through your use of the Extension that is non-personal and cannot identify a person (“**Non-Personal Data**”). If we combine Personal Data with Non-Personal Data, the combined data will be treated as Personal Data for as long as it remains combined.

We may process different forms of Personal Data depending on our lawful basis that we use to process such Personal Data. The following are a few examples of the lawful basis that we use in order to process your Personal Data: (i) we will ask for your **consent** to process your Personal Data if we are required to do so in accordance with applicable law; (ii) we may process your Personal Data if we have a **legitimate interest** to process such Personal Data for example: we may process your IP address for operational purposes, as shall be further explained below.

The table below explains the type of data we collect and how such data is used:

| The type of data we collect | How we use it |
| --- | --- |
| When you install or use the Extension, we will collect and process certain online identifies, for example your IP address. | We will use this data in order to operate and provide you with the Extension and to customize and improve it. We will also use this data to assist us in implementing the advertisements incorporated within the Extension (where applicable). For example, your IP address may be used to determine your location and thereby assist us in displaying relevant advertisements that will be suited for your needs. Additionally, we may process this data in order to track usage, statistics and traffic flow, detect fraud, or any other security or technical issues that may arise in connection with the Extension as well as for our internal analytical and statistical purposes. |
| We may collect some of your search history such as the certain search queries, which in most cases are aggregated Non-Personal Data, however, sometimes web browsing data contains terms that could be considered to be Personal Data. This data is deleted shortly after we collect it. | We will use this data for the purpose of providing you with our services that are available through the Extension (including relevant advertising based on previous searches that you have done). |
| If you voluntarily contact us, you may be required to provide us with certain information such as your name and email address. | We will use and process this data in order to provide you with the support that you have requested or in order to respond to any questions that you may have. We may store this contact history in order to improve our services, as well as to resolve disputes (if relevant). |
| When you install the Extension on your device, we may collect Non-Personal Data, such as technical information that is automatically transmitted to us by your device. Examples of such technical information may include: the type of device, browser and operating system you use, the language that you use the Extension in, and when and where you access the Extension from. | We use this data to provide and enhance the Extension and to enable its operation. |

Who Will We Share Your Data With?
---------------------------------

We will **not** share your Personal Data that we collect and process except under the following circumstances:

* (i) We may share your Personal Data with our trusted service providers as is necessary in order to allow such service providers to perform certain services on our behalf (please see “Third Part Content” section below.
* (ii) We may share your Personal Data in order to comply with any applicable law or regulation (or if permitted by any applicable law or regulation) – including our policies and agreements, legal process, or any governmental request.
* (iii) We may share your Personal Data in the event of a corporate transaction for example, in the event of a merger, asset sale, consolidation or acquisition. The acquiring company will assume the rights and obligations as described in this Privacy Policy under any of the above circumstances and we will provide you with prominent notice in such event.
* (iv) We may share your Personal Data when you have given your consent for us to do so or otherwise request us to do so. However, please note this information will NOT include any Personal or Non-Personal Information collected or processed through the Chrome Extension.

Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
---------------------------------------

Our service providers may use cookies and similar common tracking technologies such as, but not limited to, web beacons, pixels, and user agents. These tracking technologies are assigned and stored on the device which you installed the Extension in the form of small pieces of information. Cookies and these other tracking technologies are very helpful and can be used for a variety of purposes, including: enabling you to navigate between pages efficiently, enabling automatic activation of specific features, and to customize your experience by providing you with relevant content for example in the form of an advertisement. Please visit: www.allaboutcookies.org to learn more about cookies.

You are able to disable cookies or limit the data collection of such cookies through the settings of your device or that are available through your browser. We have included links to instructions as to how you can disable or limit cookies for a variety of frequently used browsers here: [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en) ; [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences) ; [Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies) ; [Safari](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265) ; [Edge](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/4027947/windows-delete-cookies) ; [Opera](https://help.opera.com/en/latest/).

It is important to note that you will not be able to prevent advertisements from being displayed entirely by disabling cookies, rather, the advertisements that you do receive, will not be customized specifically for you. Furthermore, it is important to note that, if you decide to disable certain cookies, this may result in certain parts of the Extension not functioning properly.

Third Party Content
-------------------

The Extension may redirect you to third party content. Such third party’s privacy policy, and not this Policy, will apply to your interaction with such content. We take no responsibility nor will we be held responsible for such third party privacy practices.  
Oath search feed is one as part of our Extension which may include its own cookies. You can learn more about Oath’s data collection policies at: [https://policies.oath.com/us/en/oath/privacy/products/searchservices/index.html](https://policies.oath.com/us/en/oath/privacy/products/searchservices/index.html) and how to opt - out or limit its data collection here: [https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/us/en/optout/](https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/us/en/optout/).

Data Retention and Security Measures
------------------------------------

Your privacy is important to us. We therefore make our best efforts to protect your Personal Data from any unauthorized use, processing, access, or disclosure. We have put a variety of security measures in place in order to protect your Personal Data which correspond with industry standards including physical, technical and administrative measures, as are required in accordance with applicable law. We will make a reasonable effort to notify you and any applicable supervisory authority if we become aware of a security breach that has affected your Personal Data, if we are required to do so by applicable law.

Unless you instruct us otherwise, we will retain the Personal Data that we collect only for as long as we need to in order to provide you with the various features that are available through our Extension and in order to operate our business. We will also retain your Personal Data if we need it in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements.

Data Subject Rights
-------------------

Data protection and privacy laws may provide you with some of the rights listed herein depending on the applicable data protection and privacy laws in your jurisdiction. Some of the main rights you may have are as follows: (i) the right to access your Personal Data; (ii) the right to ensure that your Personal Data is accurate, complete and up-to-date; (iii) the right to have your Personal Data amended (by asking us to correct, delete, or add information); (iv) the right to withdraw consent, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice; (v) the right to object or limit the processing of your Personal Data; (vi) the right to ask us to “port” or send your Personal Data to a third party; (vii) the right to request that we erase your Personal Data that we hold (otherwise known as the right to be forgotten) ;and (viii) the right to file a complaint to a supervisory authority (in the event you are EEA (as such term is defined below) resident). If you wish to exercise any or all of the above rights, please fill in the data subject request form available [here](https://www.becovi.com/rform.php) and send it to our privacy team at: [\[email protected\]](https://www.becovi.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

We may request that you send us proof of your identity to enable us to verify your identity in order to enable us to fulfil your request, subject to applicable legal requirements. We will respond to your request within thirty (30) days (subject to applicable law) from the receipt of the relevant requested evidence.

Transfer of Personal Data
-------------------------

We may hold or process your Personal Data in the European Economic Area (“**EEA**”), in AWS servers in the EU. Nonetheless our employees from various territories may have access to data in order to enable the Services. Subject to applicable law, we will take the reasonable steps necessary in order to ensure that your Personal Data receives adequate protection if we need to transfer it outside of your jurisdiction which include, among others Standard Contractual Clauses (“**SCC**”) approved by the European Union. If you would like to understand more about these arrangements and your rights in connection therewith, please contact us.

Children
--------

Our Extension is not meant to be used by children under the age of 16. We do not knowingly process children’s Personal Data. Please contact us at: [\[email protected\]](https://www.becovi.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) if you become aware or believe that we collected or processed the Personal Data of a child.

Contact Us for Further Questions
--------------------------------

Please contact us at: [\[email protected\]](https://www.becovi.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) if you have questions about this Policy, your privacy rights or our privacy practices. You may also contact us at:

Becovi Ltd  
5TH Floor, Nova Atria North, Blackthorn Road, Sandyford Business Park, Sandyford, Dublin D18F5X2, Ireland

Last Modified: Jan 4th, 2021
